本字幕由YYeTs字幕組原創翻譯
www.ZiMuZu.tv 歡迎交流
打開微信   掃描左側二維碼
或搜索公眾號:    ustvboom
了解最新影視字幕發布信息
饑餓
的青春
第二季  第九集
好了  艾略特  就是今天了
This is it, Elliot. Today is the day.
我要這樣做  我絕對要這樣做
I'm doing this. I am definitely doing this.
你會很出色的
And you're gonna be wonderful.
你要做什么
What are you doing?
告訴加比我對她的感受
Telling Gabi how I feel about her.
庫珀今晚就飛來了
Cooper's flies in tonight,
我得趕在他來之前告訴她
so I gotta get to her before he does.
我看了她喜歡的所有浪漫喜劇  尋找靈感
I've watched all of her favorite rom-coms as inspiration.
我知道哈利是怎么遇見莎莉的
I know how Harry met Sally,
知道西雅圖為什么有不眠夜
and I know why they're sleepless in Seattle,
我搞不明白的是怎么告訴加比我愛她
What I can't figure out is how to tell Gabi I love her.
-你為什么不說這些  -什么
- Why don't you tell her that? - What?
剛才那番話  很動聽
That speech. It was beautiful.
的確有點動聽
It was kind of beautiful.
我們走吧
Come on, let's do this.
你不能跟我一起去
You're not coming with me.
我知道  我想要你送我去埃蘭家
I know. I want you to drop me off at Alan's.
他說要給我看一個"大東西"
He said he had something big to show me.
上次他這樣做時  我笑了一周
And the last time he did that, I was smiling for a week.
我也許該穿條好褲子
I should probably throw on some pants.
我來幫忙
I'll help.
早上好
Good morning.
謝謝你讓庫珀住這里
Thank you so much for letting Cooper live here.
是待在這里
Stay here.
好吧  待在這里  直到他找到工作
Right, stay here until he gets a job.
重點是我們要住在一起了
The point is, we're living together.
是待在一起
Staying together.
天啊  是他
Oh my god, it's him.
他隨時都可能來
He'll be here any minute.
天啊  他隨時都可能來
Oh my god, he'll be here any minute!
我怎么有時間化好
How am I gonna have time
全部妝  讓自己看起來自然呢
to put on all my makeup so I look natural?
他來了
It's him.
我是超級庫珀熊
I'm super Cooper bear,
我等不及用爪子...
and I can't wait to put my paws on--
行了  我是索菲亞
Okay, it's Sofia.
庫珀  你什么毛病啊
Cooper, what the hell is wrong with you?
你上次過來的時候跟我保證過
The last time you were here, you promised me
會告訴加比喬什喜歡她
that you would tell Gabi that Josh had feelings for her.
你求我讓你告訴她
You begged me to let you tell her,
我當時想照顧你的感情
and I was sensitive to your feelings.
我本來打算告訴她  然后她說她愛我
I was about to tell her, and then she told me that she loved me.
我要怎么說啊
What was I supposed to say to that?
我也愛你  順便說一句  喬什也是
"I love you too. By the way, so does Josh"?
我給你最后一次機會
Okay, I'm gonna give you one last chance.
如果你今天還不說  老娘就說
If you don't tell her by the end of the day, I'm gonna.
我還以為海關搜身下手重呢
I thought the T.S.A. was rough.
你在這里干什么
What are you doing here?
我從中國過來跟加比同居
I came from China to live with Gabi.
該你了
Your turn.
我從我家來跟加比談談
I came from my house to talk to Gabi.
有意思  這次你走前門
Oh, interesting. And you used the front door this time,
翻譯  冰藍  roaddog
不走逃生梯了嗎
not the fire escape?
校對  roaddog
對  沒錯
Oh, yeah. Yeah, that's right.
時間軸  小獄
我知道  我都知道了
I know. I know it all,
后期  斯人   總監  roaddog
包括你愛加比這一事實
including the fact that you love Gabi,
而你對我撒謊了  說你不愛她
which you lied to me about and told me you didn't.
什么  你怎么...
What? How do you--?
什么
What?
索菲亞說漏嘴了
Sofia accidentally told me.
所以我知道一切  沒有秘密了
So I know everything. No secrets.
加比知道嗎
All right, does Gabi know?
好吧  就一個秘密
Okay, one secret.
就是說你沒告訴她  你為啥不告訴
Which means you didn't tell her. Why didn't you tell her?
因為你害怕如果她發現我喜歡她
Because you're scared if she finds out I have feelings for her,
她就會選我  我
she'll choose me. Me.
她會嗎
Will she, though?
因為我確定當她讓我住在這里
Because I'm pretty sure when she asked me to live here
并說她愛我時  是因為她選擇了我
and told me she loved me, it 'cause she chose me.
我
Me.
庫珀  我剛下床...
Hey, Cooper, I just rolled out of--
喬什  你在這里干什么
Josh, what are you here for?
我告訴你我來不是干什么的  審訊
I'll tell you what I'm not here for-- an interrogation.
你知道什么讓我惡心嗎
You know what makes me sick?
如果不是我  她都不會
It's that she never would have even met Cooper
遇見庫珀  該死
if it wasn't for me, damn it.
我得想想下一步該怎么做
I gotta figure out my next move.
擦窗戶怎么樣
How about the windows?
尤蘭達  我是認真的
Yolanda, I'm serious.
我要怎么做
What am I gonna do?
我告訴你要怎么做
I'll tell you what you're gonna do.
按兵不動  庫珀剛回來
Nothing. Cooper just got back.
加比現在很粘他
Gabi's all hot and bothered and into him.
但那孩子沒工作
But the boy's got no job,
一間小公寓住著三個人
and three people in that tiny apartment--
看看那朵玫瑰花會多快凋謝吧
Watch how fast that bloom falls off that rose.
一整天都看不到你  我要怎么過啊
How am I gonna make it through a whole day without seeing you?
那就只能給你深情一吻  讓你記住我了
I guess I'll just have to give you something to remember me by.
天啊
Oh my damn.
那并不意味著什么
Oh, that doesn't mean anything.
各位  沒看見你們呢
Hey, guys. Didn't see you there.
喬什  今早我們都沒機會聊聊
Josh, we didn't have a chance to catch up this morning.
你怎么樣
How are you doing, buddy?
還是富得流油  你呢  庫珀
Still filthy rich. How about you, Cooper?
做愛太多有點累
Other than a little tired
其余沒什么好抱怨的
from having so much sex, can't complain.
希望你別太累
Well, I hope you're not too tired.
我聽說找工作很累人的
I hear looking for work can be exhausting.
當然啦  我不知道  我一般是雇人的
Of course, I wouldn't know. I usually do the hiring.
實際上  我可以輕松找到工作
Actually, I could easily get a job,
因為我是個天才
'cause I'm, you know, a genius.
但我六個月都不能找技術工作
But I can't take a tech job for six months
因為我跟上家公司簽了非競爭條款
because I have a non-compete clause from my last company.
所以沒必要競爭  喬什
So there's just really no point in competing, Josh.
是啊  但是庫珀可以做自由職業者
Yeah, but Cooper can get freelance stuff.
所以我把我的車給他了
That's why I gave him my car.
他今天要去找工作
He's gonna go out to look for a job today.
沒工作也沒車
No job and no car?
最多一周
I give it a week.
埃蘭給我看了他的大驚喜
Well, Alan showed me his big surprise.
他清算了退休帳戶
He liquidated his retirement account
買了一家KTV
and bought a karaoke bar.
我是亞洲基佬  依然覺得那是個愚蠢的主意
I'm gay and Asian, and still think that's a stupid idea.
我覺得他想實現夢想很棒好嗎
Hey, I think it's exciting he's following his dream.
埃蘭該讓庫珀來干那些技術活
Ooh, Alan should hire Cooper to do all the technical stuff.
我的確在畢業舞會上弄過激光秀
I did put on a laser show at my prom.
效果圖比實際好多了
It was way better than actually going.
庫珀也幫喬什工作過
And Cooper worked for Josh
表現也很好  對嗎  喬什
and he did a great job. Right, Josh?
是
Yes.
好吧
Fine.
但我希望你的報酬
But I hope you work
能像你女友穿得一樣廉價
as cheap as your girlfriend looks in that outfit.
我更便宜
Cheaper.
叮叮叮  午飯來嚕
Ringy-dingy! I got your lunch thingy.
我在三明治里放了
I put crinkle cut potato chips
你喜歡的扭扭薯條
in the sandwich just like you like--
-就像我在說...  -我愛你
- Just my little way of saying-- - I love you.
-什么  -沒什么
- What? - Nothing.
好吧
Oh, okay.
我要回廚房了
Well, I'm gonna head back to the kitchen.
我愛你
I love you.
好吧  先說清楚...
Okay, just to clarify--
你是在跟我說話還是跟三明治
are you speaking to me or the sandwich?
加比  我一直在等合適的機會
Gabi, I've been waiting for the right time
跟你說  現在好像不太合適
to tell you this. Not sure this is it.
但我愛你
But I love you.
你笑什么
Why are you laughing?
我不知道該說什么
I don't know what to say.
不如說
How about,
"我也愛你  喬什"
"I love you too, Josh"?
抱歉  抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我真的受寵若驚
That's super sweet and super flattering.
所以我要說  謝謝你
So I'm going to say thank you
然后回廚房了
and head back to the kitchen.
享受你的午餐吧
So enjoy your lunch.
好吧  我現在又想了一下
Okay, now that I had a moment to think about it,
你這話怎么冒出來的
quick question, where the hell did that come from?
突然平白無故的
I mean, suddenly, out of the clear blue,
你就跟我說了這話嗎  干嘛選現在
you tell me something like that? I mean, why now?
為什么是現在
Why now?
當然了
Of course.
因為我和庫珀在一起  讓你要瘋了
'Cause I'm with Cooper. And it's driving you crazy
因為你那么好勝
Because you're so competitive.
對你來說  我就是個榮譽獎杯
To you, I'm just a trophy to win.
你猜怎么著  我才不是獎
Well, guess what. I'm no prize.
好吧  我是獎
Okay, all right, I am a prize,
但不是你的獎
but not yours.
享受你的午餐吧
Enjoy your lunch.
你好大的膽子  知道嗎
I mean, how dare you, you know?
我現在那么幸福
I'm happier than I've ever been.
你卻說了這話
And you say something like this
想來擾亂我腦子  你猜怎么著
to try and mess with my head. Well, guess what.
我腦子才不亂  實際上  無比清醒
My head is not messed. In fact, it's clearer than ever.
我愛庫珀
I love Cooper.
還以為她又要回來
Hmm, thought she was coming back.
天啊  索菲亞  我今天這班上得真瘋狂
Oh my god, Sofia, I had the craziest day at work.
我給喬什午餐做了三明治
I brought Josh in a sandwich for lunch
接著突然之間  他說"我愛你"
and then all of a sudden he said "I love you."
太好了
Yes!
的確很瘋狂哈
That is a crazy day at work.
你一定震驚到了  他提了我名字嗎
You must have been totally shocked. Did my name come up?
沒有  為什么要提你
No. Why would your name come up?
因為我是你閨蜜  你什么都告訴我
Because I'm your best friend and you tell me everything,
所以告訴我吧
so tell me everything.
好吧  你不會相信的
Okay, you're never gonna believe this,
但他跟我說他愛我  我什么感覺都沒有
but when he told me that he loved me, I felt nothing.
-沒有嗎  -沒有
- Nothing? - Nothing.
你知道沒感覺感覺有多好嗎
Do you know how good it felt to feel nothing?
你知道我原來多喜歡他的
I mean, you know how into him I was.
但現在沒感覺了  真的沒了  我愛庫珀
But now it's gone. It's totally gone. I love Cooper.
天啊  我解放了
Oh my god, I'm off the hook.
我們解放了  你解放了
We're off the hook. You're off the hook.
這事算完了
This is off the hook!
好了  我去換衣服準備和我愛的男人
Okay, I'm gonna go change to have dinner with the man I love--
庫珀吃晚餐  不是喬什哦
Cooper, not Josh. Yay!
耶
Hell yay!
這些是給我的嗎
Oh, are those for me?
不  是給加比的
No, they're for Gabi,
因為你比我今晚跟她攤牌喬什的事
because you're making me tell her about Josh tonight.
這花該給我
Well, they should be for me,
因為我有好消息告訴你
because I'm about to tell you some great news.
你今晚不用跟她攤牌了
You don't have to tell her about Josh tonight.
你問為什么嗎
Oh, why, you ask?
因為今天
Because today
喬什說自己愛她  是不是好棒
he told her he loves her. Isn't that great?
怎么就棒了
How is that great?
說實話  這簡直讓我想砸墻
Honestly, that makes me want to punch a wall.
好吧  淡定  硬漢
Okay, calm down, macho.
我不是沒見過你的寵物小精靈牙刷
I've seen your pokemon toothbrush.
好棒是因為  首先
Look, it's great because, first of all,
她不愛他  愛的是你
she doesn't love him. She loves you.
其次  我們不用告訴她了
And second of all, we don't gotta tell her.
我們不用告訴...
We don't have to tell--
我們不用告訴她了
We don't have to tell her!
沒錯  但你再喊的話  就要了
Yeah, but if you keep screaming it, we will.
抱歉  這真不錯
Sorry, sorry. This is great.
如果秘密不再是秘密
If the secret is no longer a secret,
我們就不用瞞著她了
we're not keeping anything from her.
該做的事做完了  我們不用告訴她
The right thing got done, and we didn't have to tell her.
-簡直是大禮  -簡直是大禮
- It's like a gift. - It is like a gift.
比那個破熊好多了
And so much better than that stupid bear.
喬什  你在這干什么  嚇死我了
Josh, what are you doing here? You scared me half to death.
我一直在想今天下午的事
Look, I've been thinking about what happened this afternoon.
-我們要談談  -不  該說的我都說了
- We need to talk. - No, I said everything I needed to say already.
庫珀正在那睡覺呢  你得走了
Cooper is sleeping right there. You need to go.
真是神經
The nerve of this guy.
給
Here you go.
天啊
Oh my god.
這是個夢  我在做夢
This is a dream. I'm dreaming.
為什么我會夢到喬什
Why am I dreaming about Josh?
因為你對我有感覺
'Cause you have feelings for me.
不  我沒有
No, I don't.
你得走了  我對你沒感覺
You have to leave. I don't have feelings for you.
我愛庫珀
I love Cooper.
-你真想讓我走嗎  -是的
- Do you really want me to leave? - Yes.
就說了你愛我
Told you you loved me.
不  我不想你在這  你走
No, I don't want you here. You have to leave.
真的嗎
Really?
那你為什么都要吻我了
Then why are you about to kiss me?
怎么  著火了嗎  小丑來了嗎
What? Is there fire? Are there clowns?
不  我剛做了個噩夢
No, I-- I just had a bad dream.
什么夢  你想說說嗎
What happened? You want to talk about it?
不  沒事
No, I'm good.
沒事
I'm good.
看招牌的效果多好
Look how great the sign turned out.
我們現在正式變成  "我唱嗎
We are now officially the "Me sing?
我不會唱  好吧"KTV了
I could never. Ok!" Karaoke bar.
夠了  你這假惺惺的歡呼是怎么回事
Okay, enough. What's with all the fake yays?
簡直像跟我第一任男友嘿咻
It's like sex with my first boyfriend.
我就是擔心
I'm just concerned.
要么KTV倒了  你傷心
Either the bar fails and you're sad,
要么很成功
or it succeeds,
你就成KTV老板了
and then you own a karaoke bar.
別怕
Fear not.
這KTV會很火爆的
This bar shall flourish.
看到沒  我說了老天眷顧我吧
See? Told you I was one of the chosen people.
小庫  燈光都接好了嗎
Hey, Coopy, are the lights all hooked up?
是的  你們準備好示范了嗎
Yep. You guys ready for a demo?
-燒錢啊  -像彩虹一樣
- Expensive. - It's like a rainbow.
美死了
I'm dying.
好了  我要出去拿點東西
Okay, I gotta run out and grab a few things.
你想讓我買幾個迪廳的燈球嗎
Oh, hey, you want me to pick up a couple of disco balls?
你覺得呢
What do you think?
埃蘭  我就是擔心你會虧本
Alan, I'm just worried you'll lose all your money.
艾略特  這是我成真的夢想
Elliot, this is my dream and it's happening.
船已經離港了
The boat's leaving the dock.
你要么跟我再見  要么跳上來一起劃
You can either wave goodbye or get in the boat and help me row.
居然是手劃船嗎
Ugh, it's a rowboat?
好吧  但你來劃
Fine, but you row.
我去吧臺邊優雅地喝大都會了
I'll go sip a cosmo adorably at the bar.
真高興你讓我來
I am so excited that you asked me
負責你的開業餐飲  埃蘭
to cater your opening night, Alan.
無骨雞翅哎
Ooh, boneless chicken wings.
你把它們做成小雞雞的樣子真可愛
It's adorable how you made them look like little penises.
那是麥克風
They're microphones.
因為這里能唱歌
'Cause of the singing.
這樣就有道理多了
That makes a lot more sense.
我肯定它們很美味
You know, I'm sure they're delicious,
但我太緊張吃不下
but I'm too nervous to eat.
你緊張什么  這KTV看起來棒極了
Why are you nervous? The bar looks great.
艾略特和我對這里有分歧
Elliot and I have been at such odds over this place.
我想讓開幕夜十全十美
I want opening night to be perfect,
就像艾略特一樣
just like Elliot.
知道嗎  他就是我的真命天子
You know, he's the one.
是  氣得讓我在洗衣房哭的天子
Yeah, the one that makes me cry in the laundry room.
埃蘭  我能問你個問題嗎
Alan, can I ask you a question?
你怎么知道誰是真命天子
How do you know which one is the one,
尤其是可能有兩個天子呢
especially if there could be two that are both the one?
不  加比比
No, Gabelah,
只會有一個
there can only be one "the one."
沒錯  你怎么能知道
Exactly. How do you know?
很簡單  是吻
It's simple. It's the kiss.
我記得第一次吻艾略特的時候
I remember when I kissed Elliot for the first time.
那是大學
We were in college.
我喝了一瓶半的預調酒
I'd had one and a half zimas,
感覺暈乎乎的
and was feeling really loose,
所以就大膽親上去了
so I just went for it.
那個吻讓我渾身酥麻
That kiss made my toes curl.
只有這樣才能知道
That's the only way you know.
所以不能點貓貓嗎
So "one potato, two potato" is out?
加比  我很高興你來了
Gabi, look, I'm glad you came by.
我覺得我們話還沒...
I don't think we finished our conv--
享用你的啤酒吧
Enjoy your beer.
喬什  真的很抱歉
Josh, I'm really sorry.
我知道那有些突然  但是...
I know that came as a shock, but--
加比  我收到你短信了  怎么啦親愛的
Gabi, I got your text. What's up, baby?
謝謝你來  索菲亞忙著上班
Thanks for coming. Sofia's stuck at work
我真的要找個人聊聊
and I really needed to talk to somebody.
在洗衣房里聊嗎
In the laundry room?
是的  我在這里躲庫珀
Yeah, I'm hiding out in here from Cooper
和人生
and life.
怎么了  親愛的
What's wrong, baby?
我現在很兩難
Well, I have a dilemma.
庫珀搬到樓上了
Cooper moved in upstairs
現在我"樓下"開始對喬什有感覺了
and now I'm starting to feel things for Josh downstairs.
媽呀
Oh my damn.
繼續
Go on.
喬什告訴我他愛我
Josh told me that he loved me.
我以為自己對他沒感覺
And I didn't think that I had any feelings for him,
但發現我有  所以跟埃蘭聊了聊
but it turns out, I do. And so I talked to Alan,
他說唯一知道那感覺
and he said the only way to find out
是否真實的辦法  是吻他
if those feelings are real, is to kiss him.
我就吻了  尤蘭達  那個吻真是...
And so I did. And, Yolanda, that kiss was...
棒呆了
Amazing.
我是這么感覺的
Well, it was for me,
所以她一定也是  對嗎
so it had to be for her too, right?
只有一個辦法能回答這問題
There's only one way for me to answer that question.
艾略特
Elliot.
她一定也是喜歡的
I mean, she had to be into it.
第二個吻  我覺得...
And the second kiss-- I felt that...
人都麻了  麻了  尤蘭達
In my toes. In my toes, Yolanda.
但我有庫珀了
But I have Cooper
他辭了中國的工作來和我一起
who quit his job in China to be here with me.
他那么貼心  關心人  又優秀
And he's so sweet and caring and wonderful.
我怎么能選喬什不要他呢
And how could I pick Josh over him?
她怎么會選庫珀不要我呢
How could she pick Cooper over me?
我那么好
I mean, I'm a catch.
聰明  又成功
I'm smart. I'm successful.
或許還能說  我有點...
And, might I say, I can be...
一點點自大
A little arrogant.
如果他覺得自己能睡遍半個舊金山的女人
If he thinks he can just sleep with half of San Francisco
來說"我愛你  加比"
and then say, "I love you, Gabi,"
還指望我說"好啊  喬什"
and I'll be like "Okay, Josh."
但是呢
But?
但感覺就在那  你知道嗎
But it's just there, you know--
那種化學反應  那種激情
that chemistry and that passion...
那種電流
That electricity.
你不能否認
You can't deny it.
我不能否認  我要怎么辦
I can't deny it. What am I gonna do?
我不能告訴你怎么辦  親愛的
Oh, I can't tell you what to do, baby.
我有偏向  我愛喬什
I'm biased. I love Josh.
我有偏向  我討厭加比
I'm biased. I hate Gabi.
但我愛你  所以祝你好運
But I love you, so good luck.
謝謝  伙計
Thanks, man.
所以你要怎么辦
So what are you gonna do?
做成熟的事
The mature thing, you know.
我準備躲在這里直到該去KTV
I'm gonna hide down here until it's time to go to the karaoke bar
期望答案能奇跡般地降臨
and just hope that an answer magically comes to me.
知道我是你我會怎么辦嗎
You know what I'd do in your situation?
投幾個硬幣進去
Put a couple of quarters in
在滾筒上爽一把
and ride the spin cycle.
喬什  要喝酒嗎
Hey, Josh. Need a drink?
-好啊  -吧臺在那
- Yeah, sure. - Cool. Bar's over there.
《心之全蝕》
Ooh, "Total Eclipse of the Heart."
是我的看家曲
That's, like, my jam.
我們該合唱
We should do a duet.
我更喜歡獨唱
I'm more of a solo act.
要開胃菜嗎
Um, appetizer?
好  謝謝
Yeah, thanks.
這些不是雞雞
They're not penises.
我沒覺得是
I didn't think they were.
是小麥克風  對嗎
They're little microphones, right?
是啊  因為這里是KTV嘛
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Because of the karaoke And the singing.
-我走了  -我留在這
- I'm gonna go. - I'm gonna stay.
真高興  你現在都是我的了
I'm so happy. You're all mine now.
什么
What?
你不是供完餐了嗎
I mean, you're done serving food?
是啊  對  都是你的了
Oh, yeah, yeah, right. All yours.
大家好
Hello, everyone.
歡迎來到"我唱嗎  我不會唱  好吧"的
Welcome to the grand opening of "Me sing?
盛大開業
I could never. Ok!"
這是我畢生的夢想
This has been my lifelong dream.
沒有我另一個
And I couldn't have done it
畢生夢想  艾略特·帕克  我也無法成功
without my other lifelong dream-- Elliot Park.
是我  我是造夢者哦
That's me. I'm a dream weaver.
我二十年前做了件蠢事
You know, I did a really stupid thing 20 years ago.
我遇到了自己的夢中情人
I found the man of my dreams,
卻從來沒告訴他我的感受
and I never told him how I felt about him.
為什么  有太多借口了
Why? I had a million excuses.
我怕被拒絕  時機永遠不對
I was afraid of rejection. It was never the right time.
我當時有女朋友
I had a girlfriend.
所以我們一直沒能在一起
So we never got together.
沒告訴你我過去的感受  讓我真的想打自己
I could kick myself for not telling you how I felt back then
因為我從心底知道你就是那唯一
when I knew in my heart you were the only one.
我們回不到過去
Well, we can't go back,
但我學到了很重要的東西
but I learned something really important.
我不會再那么傻了
I'm never gonna be that stupid again.
艾略特·帕克
Elliot Park,
你愿意和我結婚嗎
will you marry me?
天啊
Oh my god.
天啊  給我的嗎
Oh my god. For me?
但愿能合適
I hope it fits.
我手胖的像海星
I have hands like little starfish.
答不答應  我膝蓋不行了
Yes or no? My knees aren't the best.
我愿意
Yes.
你還好嗎
Is everything okay?
不好
No.
你想一個人靜靜嗎
Do you want me to leave you alone?
不
No.
我真的很高興庫珀回來了
I was really, really happy that Cooper was here.
可然后你說你愛我
And then you told me that you loved me
一切又亂了
and everything got confused.
然后我吻了你  你又吻了我
And then I kissed you and you kissed me
然后我就更亂了
and then I got even more confused.
然后我聽到了埃蘭的話
And then I heard Alan's speech.
我不再困惑了
I'm not confused anymore.
喬什
Josh,
是你
it's you.
不  等等
No, wait.
我得先和庫珀談談
I have to talk to Cooper first.
我最不想的就是讓他難堪
I mean, the last thing I want to do is embarrass him.
太遲了
Too late.
庫珀  對不起
Cooper, I'm so sorry.
不  我才是覺得對不起的那個
No, I'm the one who's sorry.
你想和喬什在一起嗎
You want to be with Josh?
沒問題
Fine.
但有些事你得先知道
But you should know something first.
喬什  你想告訴她嗎
Josh, you want to tell her?
你猜怎么著  讓我說吧
You know what? Let me.
-庫珀  不要  -別對我說不要
- Cooper, don't. - Don't "Don't" Me.
加比  在你被喬什的"我愛你"迷惑前
Gabi, before you fall for Josh's big "I love you,"
你該知道他三個月前就覺得自己愛你了
you should know that he thought he loved you three months ago,
就在取消自己的婚禮前
right before he called off his wedding.
沒錯
Oh, yeah.
他跟說有人都說了  除了你
And he told everybody but you,
然后  當他改變了主意
and then, when he changed his mind,
又說服所有人騙你
convinced everyone to lie to you about it.
尤蘭達騙了你  艾略特騙了你
Yolanda lied. Elliot lied.
就連索菲亞都是
Even Sofia lied,
在他送她了一臺新手機以后
only after being bought off with a new cell phone.
所以今天我們才會這樣
Which brings us to today,
現在我們在一起  他又突然愛你了
when all of a sudden he loves you again now that we're together.
我好奇這次能有多久
I wonder how long it'll last this time.
總之  我祝你幸福
Anyway, I-- I wish you all the best.
看到沒  我也可以騙人
See? I can lie too.
是真的嗎
Is it true?
加比  一切我都能解釋
Gabi, I can explain everything.
-天啊  是真的  -加比  等等
- Oh my god, it is true. - Gabi, wait.
不  你給我讓開
No, get the hell away from me.
埃蘭和艾略特
幸福永遠
好了  下一首是喬希
Okay, next up we have Josie
帶來的《餓狼》
singing "Hungry Like the Wolf."
幸虧這泡沫愛心
Thank god I didn't pay retail
我是打折買的
for that styrofoam heart.
對不起
I'm sorry.
我想今晚對你來說是完美的
I wanted tonight to be perfect for you.
就是啊
It was.
不光是加比哭著從這里跑出去
And not just because Gabi ran out of here crying.
我的戒指也很美
My ring is beautiful.
是個小蝴蝶結  因為你就是我的小蝴蝶結
It's a tiny bowtie, 'cause you're my tiny bowtie.
抱歉我之前那么嘮叨你買這地方
I'm sorry I was so bitchy about you buying this place.
我錯了  這里人山人海
I was wrong. This place is packed.
我覺得這里會很火的
I think we have a hit on our hands.
我知道  想想我開始對酒水食物
I know. And imagine how much money we'll make
收費以后我們能賺多少吧
once I start charging for food and drinks.